export const data = {
  activeExam1: false,
  activeLengua: true,
  activeLogic: true,
  activeMat: true,
  alumnData: { carrera: "DNAM" },
  lengua: [
    { pregunta: "", respuesta: "" },
    { respuesta: "A", pregunta: "58" },
    { pregunta: "59", respuesta: "C" },
    { pregunta: "", respuesta: "" },
  ],
  logico: [
    { pregunta: "", respuesta: "" },
    { respuesta: "A", pregunta: "58" },
    { pregunta: "59", respuesta: "C" },
    { pregunta: "", respuesta: "" },
  ],
  matematico: [
    { pregunta: "", respuesta: "" },
    { respuesta: "A", pregunta: "58" },
    { pregunta: "59", respuesta: "C" },
    { pregunta: "", respuesta: "" },
  ],
  test: [
    { pregunta: "", respuesta: "" },
    { respuesta: "A", pregunta: "58" },
    { pregunta: "59", respuesta: "C" },
    { pregunta: "", respuesta: "" },
  ],
  time: 10373,
  user: "MUymMC8LrBdY6X7lkof43omGgoU2",
  username: "LIZBETH RODRIGUEZ MUÃ‘OZ",
};
